

THIEN DO PHU

(+84) 932 167 244 dpthien48@gmail.com Tan Binh, Hochiminh city

A fresh graduate student with enthusiasm, activeness, hard-working and strong willing to learn. Having the excellent ability to work both independently and as a member of a team. Keen to find a Medical Representative position within an ambitious company where I will be able to increase my work experience & develop my skills

Education

University of medicine and pharmacy 2012 – 2017

DELF A2 Certificate 2015

Bachelor of pharmacy

Major: Medical Management and Supply

Experience

Green Summer Volunteer Campaign (Da Phuoc, Binh Chanh District)

2013 - 2015

Leader

- Scheduled and sold products together with the team to raise fund up to 34 million dong in a month
- Single-handedly sent the sponsorship invitation, contacted with potential sponsor for project "The Childhood Bookcase" with over 1000 children's book and gave it to Nguyen Van Tran Primary School.
- Coordinated with local authorities to organize all the activities for 21 days of operation: Health care
 program, providing free medical exams and drugs for civilians; awarding scholarships to disadvantaged
 children; visiting & taking care of Vietnamese heroic Mother; ...

District 11 hospital, Nguyen Trai hospital, Viet Phuoc pharmacy May 2017 – Jun 2017 Trainee

- Self-equipped with knowledge about the pharmacy's main activities in hospital
- Practiced dispensing, selling drugs & advising patients about drugs

Activities/ Achievements

Pharmacy Art club

Sep 2012 - Aug 2014

Dance group Leader, organized & motivated a group of 20 members, choreographed & performed at University, won 1st prize in Pharmacy's got talent 2013

1st prize in Vietnam University Games - Sport: Dance battle

May 2013

La Fête de la Francophonie 2014 - Organized by University of Education, AUF & CREFAP Member of art team

Pharmacy Social Work club

2013 - 2015

Collaborator, participated in many activities: "Khoanh Khac Yeu Thuong" (Cycling and giving gift for disabled), "Ve Nguon" (Visiting and taking care of homeless elderly in Binh Khanh, Can Gio District), ...